(Penny:)Oh, don't worry, I won't.
(Amy:)Thanks.
"The woman at the wall store?"
Let it go!
(Sheldon:)Are you going to confront Penny?
(Leonard:)Eventually, I guess.
(Leonard:)Although, I am kind of curious
how long she thinks
(Leonard:)she can keep hiding my stuff
without me knowing.
(Sheldon:)Hmm.
(Sheldon:)You know, perhaps
instead of confronting them,
(Sheldon:)we should see how far
they're willing to spin
(Sheldon:)their tangled webs.
(Sheldon:)Like that
Spider-Man action figure
(Sheldon:)that used to be on your desk.
(Leonard:)Oh, my God, I'm going blind.
(Sheldon:)Hi.
Food's here.
(Howard:)Oh.
(Sheldon:)Excellent.
(Sheldon:)I'm very hungry.
Yeah, speaking of which,
(Sheldon:)what's going on
with your apartment?
(Amy:)Oh, uh, they're still
working on it.
(Sheldon:)Interesting.
(Sheldon:)Very interesting.
(Penny:)Yeah, we swung by her apartment
on the way to the restaurant,
(Penny:)and they're gonna be fixing it
for a while.
(Sheldon:)Wait, uh...
you saw her apartment?